# Bogdan Evropin (Bohdan Yevropin) 23 y.o.

## **Python Developer**

Math and physics tutor for pupils (3+ years), helper (preparation and assistance) with exams and modules (5 years), non-commercial experience python developer (2+ years), solve a lot of Euler-project tasks in python. Making projects on UpWork for 1 month. During school-time have successful results in regional, Ukrainian and International physics and mathematics competitions.

Ukraine : Kyiv; Uzhgorod

+380 989368993
Telegram: Mind\_Root
bogdanevropin@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bogdanevropin/ https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~01dfb23f7

f1ea8ea04

https://github.com/bogdanevropin/ https://dou.ua/users/bogdan-evropin/ https://www.fiverr.com/share/LKY4dj

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**02.2022 – now: UpWork** (python simulations, modeling, math apps)

08.2021 – now: <u>learning Django</u> by Mosh Hammedani course on codewithmosh.com

00.2022 – 03.2022: 1) Scripts for Japanese painting puzzle app (backend) and was planning to make web-app. 2) Parent control helper app for children, witch could help control time of usage each app per day, having rest for eyes, making exercises and breaks, cooling PC when it is too hot.

2019 – 2021: Solved 49 Euler project tasks and some Timus tasks during python studying) when was reaching Bachelor's diploma of Applied physics (105) in Taras Shevchenko National university of Kyiv University on faculty of Radio physics and computer system (fRECS) in 2021

**Euler project**: MindAbuzer, key:

1660259 FPWyU38rWGHZ4E28rg8egudMsNG9jD7S

Used HFSS simulation for Bachelor's diploma about microwave permittivity in microwave length

2007 – 2016: Studied in Lyceum № 171 Leader. Had good results in team and single competitions (1-2 places every math and physics 3 Stage (in city) competition)

2018 – now: Teaching pupils math and physics as a tutor. In 2019 passed through a teacher course (preparation assistance before Ukrainian EIT) in Yavkurse center, but didn't accept working conditions and didn't work in this company 2017 – 2021: Helping students with exams preparations, Modules/Colloquiums and small tasks

#### **HARD SKILLS**

<u>Python</u> fundamentals, algorithms, <u>data structures</u> Classes, <u>OOP</u>, <u>SOLID</u>, exceptions, modules, packages, <u>std library</u>,

Pip, Pypi, Pipenv.

+ JSON, SQLite, CSV etc.

<u>Django</u> fundamentals, database, ORM, bootstrap, html, basics of API Basics of C++

GIT (GitHub, GitGUI etc.)

Clean PEP-8 code by using principles:

KISS, DRY, YAGNI, Single responsibility, document code, understandable comments (<u>B2 Upper-Intermediate English</u>). **UA & RUS are native**.

IDE: <u>PyCharm, VsCode</u>

Basic ML principles:

Supervised / Unsupervised, basics types of algorithms and models

Physicist skills: microwave physics, standard Mechanic, math physics,
electrodynamics, statistical physics, quant physics, basic atomic physics, soft:
HFSS simulations

<u>Mathematician skills</u>: Linear algebra, higher math, deferential equations, TFCV, statistics and probability theory, combinatorics, discrete mathematics, basics of game theory, soft: <u>MathCAD</u>, <u>Wolfram-Alpha</u>, <u>Maple</u>

### **SOFT SKILLS**

Simply find <u>ways to communicate</u>: easily and <u>understandably explain my thoughts</u> (was pupils Tutor for more than 3 years)

#### **HOBBIES**

Philosophy, reading books, listening music, writing rap, playing guitar

## **EDUCATION**

**2021 – Now:** Resumes reaching Master degree of Applied physics (105) in Taras Shevchenko National university of Kyiv on faculty of Radio physics and computer system (fRECS)

**2021:** Reached Bachelor's diploma of Applied physics (105) in Taras Shevchenko National university of Kyiv on faculty of Radio physics and computer system (fRECS)

2016: Graduated from school: Lyceum № 171 Leader